Caleb Hebert

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/calebhebert | https://github.com/ctrl-alt-caleb | <a href="https://github.com/ctrl-alt-caleb | <a href="https://github.com/ctrl-alt-caleb | <a href="https://github.com/ctrl-alt-caleb | <a href="https://github.com/ctrl-alt

Professional Summary

Air Force Veteran completing four years of honorable service with an active TS/SCI security clearance with 4 years of experience in server and systems administration. Diligent and detail-oriented problem solver seeking to transfer this knowledge to the software development process to provide clean, maintainable code, as well as an intuitive and enjoyable user experience.

Projects

Drone Attack - https://ctrl-alt-caleb.itch.io/drone-attack

Published 2D game built with C# in the Unity engine.

- Developed class relationships in object-oriented projects
- Implemented unit tests and multi-platform optimization
- Created design documents for project specifications
- Integrated Git for version control

Skills

C#; JavaScript; HTML; CSS; Unity; Azure; MS SQL Server; Active Directory; MVC; Teamwork & Collaboration

Professional Experience

07/2022 - 11/2022

Microsoft Software and Systems Academy, Microsoft

- Employed the .NET framework with C# for object-oriented programming, debugging tools, I/O programming, performance and memory management, database access and data encryption
- Styled and modified webpages with JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3
- Deployed functioning, flexible and scalable applications in a cloud environment

04/2018 - 07/2022

Virtual Desktop Infrastructure Engineer, *United States Air Force*

- Planned and coordinated installation, testing, operations, patching, troubleshooting, and maintenance of Windows and Linux based hardware and software servers and client systems
- Implemented PowerShell script to reduce vulnerability patching time by 70%
- Managed VDI environment; configured VMware vSphere, VMware Horizon, and SecureView systems supporting over 15,000 personnel across 9 bases
- Performed vulnerability management on critical joint planning software; eliminated hundreds of vulnerabilities including DOD's #1 cyber vulnerability across 4 bases on 24 virtual servers

Education

08/2019 – present

Computer Science B.S, Hawaii Pacific University (90 credit hours completed)

Coursework: Computer Programming; Databases; Algorithms; Operating Systems;
Statistics; Calculus I & II

Certifications

2022	IT Specialist – Software Development
2018	CompTIA Security+

Awards

Air Force Achievement Medal (2x), United States Air Force Action Officer of the Quarter, United States Air Force Airman of the Quarter, United States Air Force